During. During.
During.
The OR.
During
rush. Hour and. Are large.
And small rural
small wall wall
rural
. Small
Luling all when
we're at war.
War. War war
during. A small role.
All wore during
all or all of the world.
All right.
We're all.
Oh.
I'll. Love you.
All right.
They always come in. All right Bob
I'm going to help with the I'll.
Just. Yeah when they. All.
Were or. Were. You
or
All right.
Blood pressure valve is all that
all right. Well we're all nest.
Egg
a lot. But. A day.
A day. During the time
I don't pay all I saw
a law led all along
a la la a little old
a little knowledge
a little Our Lord.
During. Her and.
I'm not touching one of them told their
friends and family then just like how many
people my God I'm so much reading and you
know we love you we love our editor and
I'll. Remember the test results and.
I'll just I'll. Ever
Marlena. Their.
Dollar. Air.
In May it will. Do you
move her resume Oh boy who
told substrate. All right
book
a movie bids me gold. Letters full moon or
hard truth so alone with my I'm serious.
Sometimes sighs tying my logs mol. More
low. Blow those
homes low warm. Words though many moons.
Hello. How do you do are you
an actress I don't know
but in the gymnasium I could see why because
you can make believe so many wonderful
things that never happen in real life and
if you like to make believe one thing.
Why can't we make believe we
know each other. A little
book. Called Dream the
world we're in. San Juan. Carlos
is saying the sweet dream
all don't harbor. Won't.
That's just stunning when I'm
told. Nic hello to me in
a role. The way. You want
Nevertheless I don't. Really need love my.
World.
The way. The nation all
the good. Sure. Ain't.
Any world we sure were
world. It could.
Be
a movie we're. World. World
would walk away with
a. Lot of. Old
Polish bombs a lot of stuff and
a good sailor moon to lose good for
a. Good known. Good or
a murdering me lol.
Well all we want. To know for
whom. Or to for all of us are they.
Certainly were Berthold Murray payware and
her was.
Some warm. During.
The.
World. Thank you. Yes mother.
I hope I see you.
It's.
The. World.
Through each.
Game.
I tell on the wicked stage ain't ever won
a girl not all told they don't or
Johnny to our great genome are you with
him and run all day when you are
lined up in our own yard which
made them act from their own words and
when I say everybody whispers ain't
heard my phone work hard. Don't
you are warned against a rule
a ruining your right. To say no
when you play around the one night
train around the brain bank maintain
a while all my no good being killed
and a bully old little boy learn
a song say balls lie down
on the way in a nominee or
a girl really. Really and you.
Really do not see him there is
no God just Tavia ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Hey.
A.J.
. Yes Janell want to talk. I
was. Told Meg. On my
song on the way to get
paid not my mother. A good
Samaritan.
Was led. By
a minute to my. Hammock. And
says you was. There I know we. All
need
a LOL I'm glad to come. It's
my home. For usenet the.
Last two months through ahead who can.
See we got us for no new
born good gotta fly.
God alone knows one may do I.
Can't narrow through love enough
that my head didn't move much.
More. The aim is to. Those we've
come. Down man crazy to rape
would say no old.
Old old women that maimed out of my
moon or world old lawyer whom he told
the way
a the black the reindeer during
a the doorway
a ha. I had. Eaten
come. See.
Him. Old.
Kang and. Remember that no
man. Oh.
Oh nice girl an
M.M.
Joby
. Need.
A. Whole subject to good
ole boys to fit in just. A.
Day. The.
Girl lolol
a bomb Iran L R
clear their wall old
girl F.E.M.A.
Early
every
ailment
a wall
a all B.S.
All BELL Well are all their bell
there. Early
a day or anywhere along any
cardiac. All or early.
Zero zero zero
zero
or
add or
are.
Iraq Iraq the real world or your lawyer
or
a wanted man or young
lawyer or iraq me or Iraq
I'm hearing you're
a warrior. Your
. World.
With us well show must a kind
of thank you Jim. That's
a walled off with. What was that you know
the big shindig it's one for you know the
walled off and. Yes. About First
I like to stop with friends if
I just. Turn right at the
next crossing and I think.
Looking for an old brownstone
house. With a home of
a very great friend. Tonight
during the shrine. And enough time
yes. And I'd like to know
your few minutes to be. An
illusion. I guess is like like
a minute or so I was like that yeah it's
just something like that. Here stop your
job here at the corner
in front of. Radio shop.
There it is. You mean at that
lodging house sandwiched in
a well of course you didn't have the room
to the sun. And other than that it hasn't
changed very much. The street
is changed changed quite
a bit since I first walked down it
years ago. Joe. You know this is
Radio Shack. Where there was a
bicycle shop the first time I have
a phone. I remember the day very
well it was spring and I might
have been any American kid
coming down the street. I had
a song into my arms my hopes were high
and the world was wonderful. I was
ambitious and I was eager but I needed
a little help. I've been
told the best ever to me was
a man by the name of Tesla Jane asked.
Tell me I'm coming in you're an hour late
already I suppose you realize that you
can start on the up stairs bedroom immediately
this is not like any working level
seats I'll be there in
a second Mr Hester and see that you get
today and this young man asked you know
what I'm
a songwriter songwriter I see you answered
under false pretenses Well I won't do
you any good young man has
a thing song like this anymore
he's going into bestie. Which
. Song. Will help. You not in
a following I don't you know you do yes
well you can come inside alive can't have
people fainting in the house not
even songwriters coming home to him.
Yesterday he's starting to do it after
just imagine. Trying to round Mr Max
Dr Fisher the harms company sent you remember
Tony things has possibilities of its
property arranged doubt the arrangement the
cards given to you why he said that he
told you that I was the greatest
arranger in American I should give you
a few lessons my friend is right there's
only one catch I've given up arranging I'm
through dressing up silly little tunes
for Girls shows in barrows I'm going to
write some real music for
a change. Here Mrs. Said And the trouble
with you songwriters is all you ever think
about is making money Saddam has no sleep
over no thank you Joy it's announce it on
you know I think of doing anything big
anything worthwhile like Brahms or bridge. I
don't dance again please
but it has this place with
a so we always keep it said oh I'm sorry.
But I want to do it right sugary little
tunes and make
a lot of money but did you ever hear
Beethoven's Eroica or Mozart's Jupiter and
then they do something to. Them and as
ingenious touch you fellows at all the idea
of doing it. And then genius. Now
my friend in three weeks I'm
doing when I can work have some peace and
quiet no mushy little melodies to be
fancied up for public consumption. I'm
going to write a symphony any kind of
a nap to just so many. Eh go ahead go
ahead eat em I mean give me some gumption
while I'm terribly sorry Mr Hester I had
a big lunch with Mr Dreyfus just
before I left. It was roast beef to
that well I know as
a matter just because you're not hungry you
don't have to go to your abs and brandy
with me helping celebrate my
liberation from mediocrity. I get
a couple of liquor glasses were you Sally
would you show Mr the gentleman into the
parlor and one abstention see
if I can find a bottle in
a Polian. And your song and. I can
piano lessons Daddy wants me to
be another thing when I get up. And up well
Sally I'm afraid I only write the silly
little tunes you know the ones your father
doesn't like let me see if I can play
a song do you mind I wish
you would very easy here.
By phone the phone color consigning
kept right right God not well it's
a name of a very romantic beach in
a wife happy. To know it be the natural.
Television. Movie union rules.
Played on and. On out on our way to magic.
That's not right you've got to use clarinets
to play the event I was thinking of
using brass air rations boy if any good
heavens man you've always got to say the
breasts of percentage are. Well what
do you think think I know this is
a romantic song sit down it's sentimental
got to start the melody off with your
strings to the zero and show you
start that vamp again Sally.
Is Perfect lately. Not in
the strings it is easy.
To hear one that is.
Out And Tom you to.
Make. Sally.
BOWLES move on I don't know what I
meant but at flutes they're like easy.
Now then add your breath. Right.
Here.
Where you say you had a Z. It's
a good sound too that's very good
and that's your guess. That's
that's what I did but your name
again Kurt and Jerome Kern.
I'm glad I made you can. Make
yourself at home. And I did my
life became
a pattern of notes pledge tempos and
modulation we worked hour after hour day have
to. Do is the beginning of the
friendship. It was the beginning
and. Now not only did I
have a best friend I had
a best girl. One of. Those women to be
forgotten days for hated to think of them
ending but at last the time came when Jim
had to leave legal and.
All your money old.
Talk a little bit of companies
of yours there is heavy and talk
a little and then at ten
a like some tunes I have
heard. All South African. The
guy yelling out what just
small but I thought. That if
you carry
a lot of weight Sally It was. Going on
down the Emmys when I got in the boat
combined with the pantomime and. The By
Sally photo Yeah he's got me haven't you.
Found where you live under all. This been
a boy the guy because now I. Need to look
all that is or something and. You know if
it hadn't been for Sally I wouldn't be
here now. He's very fond
of you Gerry I've got
a mission. With him it's all. Of you
not be gone so long it all depends
on. Won't mind living here alone with
you oh no no I'll get used to it.
Jim in case I don't get
a chance to build. I just
want to. Get I I like
arranging now that I'm through with.
That eventually I know it's more than
a spend your kindness and your only. A
Jerry. I just want you to write some good
music some real easy and saw things don't
don't waste your time fussing those with
the little to spank they try to be
so I will try to be as big as I can.
Be on our way. Oh. My right.
Now I start technology
remember that. Your son to.
Iraq.
I stood there watching that boat pull out
of the harbor and I was lonely of the
night ever been in my life. I walked through
the days that followed from office to
office here to see that always getting
the same discouraging as. The big hits
were all English or European and the.
Local talent just didn't seem to have
a chance. Broadway was closed to Americans.
From Twenty third Street to Times
Square and the old plain monolithic.
Medium with Charlie Rose.
And he's with Cal that's so cal and the
English composer Mr Frum is not interested
in American songs at the moment
he's leaving for England in
a few weeks. Good day. How do you do My
name is current your own current all you do
is how do you do so I think you have the
deeds with you Mr Frohman very anxious to
see them eat you with a man from the
real estate office and you know I'm
a songwriter these are some of my songs
your name isn't Kern No Kurt Jerome Curry
I'm sorry Mr Frohman happens
a minute to waste time afraid I must say
goodbye maybe if you listen to one of my
songs I have one that could
be made very good days.
By the problem by Mrs Keller I'll see you
in London soon I'll call you when I get
there thank you I'll be
waiting for your call.
I made up my mind that I was going to try
to write music with an English accent so
I sailed for London I wish I could say
with flags flying in my car. But the C.
And I and the boat. Get along to meld
together. I was mighty glad to see London to
.
Excuse me if you tell me where Mr has to
lead case now the adults with the evidence
Mr know I have to start Mr
Chairman Hasler. Telling. Me until
God. You know I didn't know
I was myself the only.
Palliatives prayer.
Well the tables it turned American
songwriter invades England.
That's pretty good Jerry that's daring
very original You're thinking they get
anyway it's
a chance I'm taking Jim. So you've got
no skin here and you. Haven't got enough
roast beef like me I guess.
Area and look at you sitting in
a chair tired for me to believe you have
a man here over time thanks to it
said sort of like being home again.
How was the symphony coming along all
right. Oh yes I'm still in the know making
stages because I always believe in making
plenty of notes it's in the. Gun like
planning seed wonder how it starts to
grow and then for you no longer hold your
symphonies all written simple and easy and
not as difficult as writing those silly
little tunes. Well do you know it's
it's the quiet here that does it your.
Piece in this place is. To float
on in. The rustic pastoral.
Tells. All the doorbell when
you get the door plate. Yeah.
There's a there's
a picture as pastoral. You
know the polls. Well OK
with the pope you know the smell of it is
almost Edwards put him on campus at the
time hello George I'm fine I don't work
tomorrow be glad to get my camera but then
are good. I George Edwards the
producer yes he wants me to
sit in on the rehearsal of
a new show you think. Out of Jerry you've
got to talk to your daughter I can't do
a thing with her any longer Well this is
one of the joys Thursday night you know me
maybe take
a lesson. Should I am going Yeah well I I
think you should have one day off maybe
you know at the end of it there was some
hope for until around code Gerry arrived
now she's full of a good
and tell me get a feel for
a cup of tea. You know Sally I'm
inclined to agree with you I
think Uncle Jerry's arrival does call for
celebration. While at the London of the
fire. They train. Right the ferret is.
If you'll. Buy
a. Camera on air
talent that. Area an area.
Like this one could be one of.
Bono No Jerry I don't want
to sell it but it's wise not to see them
or the whole stage full of swings in
a boy and girl in each way all
of them six. Oh you mean for
a production Yeah. It's not
a bad idea they get swayed from the stage
right out over the audience to the max.
It's because. What what song
is used to dealing with
a perfect. Bully and that sounds Suppose
I take it up to Georgia for the gays to
come and have dinner with
him tomorrow night Archer.
Thank.
You. I don't know why I am somebody
Sean I know when I was a
meteorite. I never loose
a lot of damage. No less
pain on Saturday with.
A knowing smile on my mind and imagine
that I nabbed dawn when my on.
My now last minute tell
you I'm. Not now just my
saw
a little. Child. Oris might.
Want to do
a little Walter. On my old Sean Sean.
Sean who knew. You were. Going
to say you know I've made
a movie. And it was. Day by
day. During. Some of.
The stuff.
Into
a new. Way
of enabling. Me and
I'll take my. Comments
on to say one last May
The world was. Egged on by.
A black eye. On
a lot of. Our jobs this is. Where all
the time to do.
Pardon me for interrupting you just
pointed out to me is the composer of that
delightful number with the swings and my
name is from Charles from it's kind of
a congratulatory from I'm sorry sir that
it is my number my name is with the Kent
of the. Gentleman there but he can't
beat it seems that it can shape me.
In many instances and on
a musician Mr Bergman I have something
here which I know you like it's
a beautiful number with castles
with all sorts of parasol.
Almost from
a how do you do I very much know you just
can I want to tell you I think your swing
numbers delight has such
a beautiful English charm to religion just.
By Jove is from that's us rather nice
of you to blatantly Mr. You
know you fellows over here have
a style all yours as English as the scent
of the May Blossom would you join me in
a glass of sherry right Joe miss.
You like it that you went on the
gate I think humans would take
a rest. If I could finish it I know I could
it was from wanted. To know by now that
Charles Freeman is only interested in
English music and English composer. I only
had
a piano I know I could work
this out right. FLATOW
Well looks like you do have
a little work to do that can we pass wasn't
very far back question no not very well
let me take your bike and I'll go back
into my car repair kit now I think I'd
better kill I can talk to the natives about
it and you can well let me do what I
can use lying and honest I just went out
and right now you wait here as we are self
a little June July come back. I'll make
sure you can find this place again I'll
find it.
I say I'm not.
Here.
How do you do. Did Mr Kent continue.
Well I was just passing by on my
bike and I got
a flat tire and only then you don't work
from escaping No I haven't noticed your
piano through the window so I thought I'd
come in and try a little too high C.
For
a minute I thought you were the piano do
you know. Well I gotta go for you. Want
you to hear a little. Well I don't know
whether anybody's told you was for
a working girl you're very pretty Thank
you you're an American are you. I'm
a songwriter has that effect that song I
was playing your game is my you like it
you wrote it you said sure why write
songs. Maybe have maybe you've heard
this one. But that's from the
gating everybody singing it ha. Now
this is the one I was working on.
Group that I'm going to try to place in
the Getty to of course I would if I were
you don't you believe I wrote
a song kill me when you come home you
always break into people's houses to borrow
their piano. I tell you what I'll do if I
places with the chaos and your tickets
you can come and see for yourself will you
I'll tell you when I get the picture. I
think of putting this to test him out I
would like to speak to you she's in the
upstairs meeting Thank you Katie
I'll be right at the ferry Well I'm.
Terribly sorry. But I still
wrote those songs and
I'll still be waiting for the tickets
when you. Wonder why I want to get
the right.
To. You with
a lead it wasn't going to
fall in love with anybody for
a long long time well this girl is different
this is here and I don't joke about it
it's serious. The Don't you believe me yes
of Coombes. As she really is different
I know and ur hair is like spun gold shining
in the semi Latin know about her hair
she had
a courage I found that her eyes her eyes
were like pools in the starlight. Even
with her working clothes on she's the
prettiest girl I've ever seen show. Seriously
Jim don't you believe me
yes. It's spring isn't it.
Tomorrow morning I think
I'm going to give you
a great big dose of sulphur and molasses.
Same. Thing.
Where. Class they.
Go by. There was quite.
Poor.
There. Was.
A. New.
From the.
Yusuf to move those.
My you you. Or are.
You. Are or are.
Or are. Aries needlessly although I have
noticed. When I look at you I can't seem
to see anything else or writing songs
again perhaps we better stop and have
lunch. You can look in under those trees
there. Isn't it
a beautiful day. Beautiful. Now
let's see if seen with Mr Abbey and the
Tower of London and you sing Buckingham
Palace at Hampton Court. Maybe there's
something I can tell you about this place.
Eva let's drop the history goes for
a while do you mind not that it isn't
interesting but well there are
a few things I'd like to know about you
too well all right what would you like to
know about me oh just the ordinary things
things you like things you don't like
where you went to school who was your first
blow and what you want out of life nets
a tall order where shall
I start things you like
a lie I guess I like what everyone likes
I like bookstand and picnics and dancing
and music what about musicians Oh certainly
musician and what he want out of life
oh I guess again what everyone wants
happiness. Have you ever given any thought to
getting married hi of course doesn't everyone
are you set on any particular type of
man I had been at different times when I
was sixteen I desperately wanted to marry
the star cricket player at rugby and now
now mum of. Now I don't really know
that they must have
a sense appealing and he must be kind he
must be intelligent good company and of
course let me near enough. Well.
I know somebody with at least one of those
characteristics. Some day I'll tell you
all about it. I'm going to afternoon good
afternoon good afternoon and how you're
going to have them tell you how I'll
have to look now I never mind you feel
wonderful you feel great how could
you be otherwise after such
a beautiful day. At jolly my friend how
was your knowledge of English history
anguish history did you know that London
happens to be the largest city in the
world I know that did you know that within
the county of law there are fourteen
roads bridges across the Thames now
there is the low lapsing sounds duller
Well it's far from dull my friend when your
history teacher is as beautiful as all
the sirens of history put together. Did
you know that all the swans on the Thames
belonged to the king of England centuries
and the male Swan is called the carpet.
What is that if you know when you walk
into Hampton Court you're walking right
straight into history Oh my dear friend
you have so many things to learn about
England have you ever heard of a man named
Charles Frohman from from a. Million
a space scapes me. How could you talk about
from and when I'm talking about love.
In the field to this little dissertation
here but I'm glad to inform fellow itself
because next time from an office call it
I'll tell him that you're too busy to be
bothered if you come by.
To say the next time from which office
calls that's what I said they've been
calling you all day why should I bore you
with such trivialities Well what do they
want no new dear friend you return to your
archives why think of the future when
the past is so glorious all come when I
put time in what happened nothing nothing
for
a moment just want you to write four songs
for his new show if of course you can spare
the time well why didn't you tell me about
it why didn't I tell you about it come
on let's get going there's no time we've
got to do that on the ship. On the watch
on the ship was sailing with Charles Frohman
tomorrow we have to start rehearsal in
six weeks in New York. Jim I.
Hope there is. This is
a chance of the way. You certainly are
opposed to privatizing should be up in the
world. If you like I've just
been yanked out of the crowd.
Just going down for lunch. You know Jim
I'm afraid. You've got to snap out
of this it isn't the end of the world it's
a beginning you're you're
on your way back home with
a child phone contract in your. You want
to feel wonderful. I know that's what I
keep telling myself you pathetic
little. If I just could of seen
a once Jerry was all we could do to catch
the boat you could you talk to her on the
phone on the phone what can you say on the
phone alone nice thing you take care of
yourself. Jim I was so
many things that I wanted
a seat on the chair you've got to think of
a new career things are just starting for
and you can say that over and over again
and you know what happens. To me
you know for the first time in my
life I'm of Iraq I am
a ship full of people with you. And I might
as well be on the devival by myself.
You have to feel its way yes once what
did you do about it. I married the girl.
On the road. To lovingly if you were
down to record no I have the first
day out old ruffled I know that Englishman
should have me see ladies by now but I
haven't been the average from and that's
something I must tell you I'm not the time
the something I miss tell you I never thought
that you were at least not after the
first fifteen minutes matter of fact I'm
very proud to be able to bridge into new
America and the World Bank I have
a lot of faith you can. Just receive the
violets we join the Sanderson she's
accepted the part of the girl from Utah
one of the first now I got to have
a break the song for. The
Love Song he's got one.
When I went oh. Oh when the new
rom.
Or remove one you know your
eyes. Your hair our M A car
a veil I. Don't know why the war.
Was. When I was.
And I'm third wheeling
all of. You all over
the water. Was. A while before.
What. A Womb is
what from what.
You've chosen.
Or.
Your. Serfs. I've
got to Klaus number three well.
I never realized that writing
a complete star with. One good all
night session like decisions wonders.
Another week. When it's released
late already. The production
team. Crazy about an. Audience
of another show or even waiting.
In line so I What are you doing
up. Right it isn't morning
already can't be bad you. Say
Jim don't you think I got
a call from
a secretary to get the point you were
calling the home to learn I want. Bryant
two four four six plays. Do you think it's
a good enough condition from here oh yeah
sure it's in good shape for first said
Hello this is Kern Jerry Curry and Mr Frohman
was expecting me to call today about
a point. He's leaving for England well but
he promised that he was going to listen
to my show oh boy for his
next project. Say is today.
All right thanks. Well that's it I don't
know what to buy I am so of another
English you know. What I can't.
No He can't we work like dogs on
this go again and I had all my plans made
to have three but I was going to jump the
next boat for England and forget
about that yeah maybe. Wait
a minute I've got. My passport is still
good why don't I take the same boat he's
taken to the wonderful getting on board
ship it can get away from us right I get
out of the show wonderful. Joining him
in a while you're probably have to ask
a first world nation are you are going
Phone seem to come right now back on the
firing line to make it alright to get
a break in traffic in the origin of all
the. Ferry Come on now with the kind of
imminent. Threat you wanted that bought
a. Chap
from
a. TRIBE watching your
company trying to. See
this kind of mission. Very lucky that
Mr Kerry. In Mike's around
although Jim Baker No I think
you might overcome second Elliot's what
a terrible tragedy Yes it's unbelievable
Gerry and I were just talking over Gerry
you know Victor Herbert Don't you this is
Jerry current account even to Jerry the
great honor to meet you Mr having so many
Romans both of you quite often they had
great hopes for you well he was very
kind he likes you but more importantly
respected you in the D.Z.
To see why you've got
a song to sing thank you. Look down
at that city Jerry. It's made up of
millions of people. Music is played
a part more well lives.
Lullabies. Love Songs him.
Anthems. Must be pretty wonderful Mr to
realize that people you don't even know and
never will know I sing your songs and all
of them asking for more victories makes
me feel grateful Jerry very humble. One
of these days you will find out yourself
outfields. What is it my publishers
call me the dean of American music.
And I think you're going to be the next
Dean. One thing I must admit you've got
a better figure for it. Writing though
I don't let anything stop you. The
night. I pictured the night
Jim. Really was very much it's
a deal Gentlemen congratulations Comstock
and Eliot are going to produce all boy
that's just send me over with
a check. For the matter of
your pile of money. Things.
Turn out those lights again with.
Well it is
a nice feel well if you're pretty good
if I could just get rid of some of these
butterflies. How do you feel I've got
a little butterfly trouble I step up.
I suppose you think wish that I was
a theater thirty nine from Brussels and
how will you take me for thirty nights in
Broadway this is the top of the world
pretty nice where the great wonderful what
a difference seeing your name in life can
make it come on we better go in will miss
the show.
Rare
a pair have PADDA. And I'd
lilacs to see if they
pan air and I'll gain
even more of the world
in a bid for
a mermaid being or often are and.
And still are
a man and she added. And awareness for
a clearer sky. Air Aaron for my
minority early or. Their first and I.
With. Little. Or. In.
The. Dorm or in.
The.
Early bird and girl that
was in the. Door and.
Then one or lend. Any.
Lyric.
To. Night.
During the filming women already.
Had
a day. There is another. Method
and I believe. In. It and
I'll add that.
Said even an Alitalia Anatole
a metal heart Clara Calif. All about.
All of the little Iraq all of
I'll tell Al.
I'll I'll I'll.
Let you said Merry Men My message
is that I. Don't always know any
money when.
I'm going to spend your money and. Well
for one thing I think I'll hide it just
hard for another. Reason might take
a little ocean voyage. Well good luck I
don't see how she can watch and listen and
that's what I worry about right she is going
to say. You know I can't get around my
. Well she's kind of into this.
She's everything you ever dreamed of. Is
everything I've ever dreamed of and have
a. Home to Yours and not
your shallow or are.
On more or.
No. Jerry than you know you
didn't write very often
well my letters were very
interesting so I told them up. As
a matter of fact you didn't
write very often yourself
a lady doesn't respond to Jasmine and
listen to reason other than a personal one
a lot now doesn't that sound
a little silly to you know it it sounds
altogether fitting in Prague. And want to
find Elaine young one well what does
a lady do oh you are impossible Well you're
right if I were you I'd have nothing to
do with me in fact if I were you when I
asked you to marry me I'd say no just on
the grounds that
a lady never says Yes Now see here are
you going to ask me to marry my with
a little courage believing
in my country if
a lady wants to be asked she has to be
encouraged in my country your country what
in your country well there are there are
other ways to go about such things in
every country. Well than let me put it
this way. From the very first moment I saw
you when you walked in from the garden I
knew that out of all the women in the
world I finally found the right one the
only one or I wanted to tell you then I
want to say hello funny thing I don't know
your name or anything about you but I'm
left with my life you are my first school
teacher my first date the first girl I
have
a kissed more than everything in the world
you see I recognized you you're caught
on that's right I stood there thinking
that wondering what you do hiking. What
would you. What would you do now.
When you married me. You.
Hello Ms You can tell my
darling.
The kind of. Welcome home.
Gym point you will find every Saturday
this time nothing live or an outing just
a little gesture Yeah. This
is even Hello you. Well
you've married the nicest
guy in this world but the craziest all now
wait a minute I was keeping them from
a as she sensationally Jim Girardi turn
around and let him look at you Gerry and
look at that hair and those
eyes Have you ever seen
a woman like that in your life the for only
once now I I hope that both of you have
all the happiness where I have to give him
I think we have already thank. You Oh
Sally Yes I'm sorry dear Sally. Yes
Justin my. Son just text me.
I want to come back here on
this tank you going to bring.
Well on behalf of my wife and myself I
thank you very happy gentlemen said I was
apparently it felt wonderful to see you
half grown up Hamish you Sally this is
you're on the five. Hundred second I find
you Sally we're going to be real good
things are new to me we are
well nobody say this is
a show going to have something be joyous
it ought to have it so good to be home
with. Yes it was good to be you know
I felt I had everything in the was
happiness success and the wife I had
dreamed about I wanted to put it all into
music even smile. And her
eyes. And what it meant to be
with her. And it lasted saying to me that
the clouds had rolled but first there
was here today was. A late June change
campaign I don't know why you see maybe
five times the U.K.'s turn Caraway It's
nice to do everything again but you know
you can when you are getting our train
fare well you gave me
a promise I'm saying it down to
eighteen years on Yom that there is not
a dotted on the left in Nairobi that
will soon get you out of it. And Mary
had
a retailer and Sharon and Oliver and yes
a rare. Rare.
Rare and well Jane why did you tell us how
you like Jacqueline. Oh but it's really
very simple I just study up on the famous
women of history you mean like the
Krishna boys. No not exactly
listen in days of old beside
the Nile they must be done for you
must follow style her behaviors.
On every man mom she pulled her barrow.
And. All that her work
was slim but Mary girl
was.
Good. Enough. Then she doesn't.
Reside in
a pair of. Pants
. And. Each time she did
them start up then.
They'd stand. And watch. Her.
It's usually
a nod I'm glad when she
went. And then my exact.
I was always on the.
Floor. Something else.
Besides Mark. Was
aware of
a lot of. You're
. Ready to engage in to the it doesn't go
away and read a lot to a little girl
a little Caylee's Law to lay it on Job
rural I'll. See the stars are in
a recession. While they're
in the gun barrel vein in.
The end so then I'll be the end all
girl in
the end.
Once again a profit way to
deal with. The George M.
Cohan big business George Gershwin
mentioned to his body to show.
I was working in my degree your position
during one of my own challenges in ballet
I was fortunate enough to have the reigning
queen of the year in the wishes of
a lovely I'm forgettable
fairly good. In the event of.
A rural area in the area
a little later on a. Great event
a little girl and that ended in
a classroom and on and on that are a very
frank exchange with my friends I have
a nice you're going to have to agree how
is it going to hold you might not be just
a little under the designer that he's the
know you're not going to do any more
fires Mr Dick said I learned how to think
and I think since the first act was
a dream. Sounds lovely which you said the
second to has you don't worry about the
second sex the heart of my heart. Your
Hazel is eviscerate if it could change
everything Freddy in
space yes and. You can.
Get a G.P.S.
Everything here just. Physics
if you like to keep. It
up now and if you think you
said. It was just other
services for. Any army standard
we're going to try to.
Prevent your living in America.
Long was much called the following
line. You know I see the
brightness than let up
a lot in common. I am sure
this point of view will
ease the David Gergen joins
me live on live T.V.
He is the moon in money and money flows.
Luke close to the moon.
And error was obviously is the most
moving. Story of them boots. What I
heard was the T.
Shirts are anything. And sold off I would
always change Hochuli and my next
job already Tuesday Oswald was.
A water hand glass and I had. Willow was
a job hunting sub. And Steve
Harvey saw all. The world
was just cost all God's law against
God and straw to us. Us.
Us. Was the.
World than woman
seemed was caught off.
Was one of us.
Or was.
Saw all.
Was hard slog God.
It's. Gone.
Was.
I never thought I would ever keep
a scrap but it was nice and neat was
singing my songs and asking for.
Night boat morning during the Ziegfeld
Follies curtains went up Christmas came down
and I think Eric out of
look a little more like
a fish. Even over
a love affair with every passing year
our life was rich and full and very
satisfying and Jim and I where we grew
a little grayer than seven
habits he was still working on
a symphony. He said. But on the whole
the years didn't change as much.
He certainly did change. Too is quite
a young lady in her. She'd been away
at school in fact many school. Well
Sally Hello darling. Now Sally
I thought you were schooled
well what I was. What happened this
time I just can't stand that school and
your own good Jerry has left and and I'm
not going that well as your father said
about that. Well he hasn't said anything
yet he he doesn't exactly know you see I
just left there this morning I came right
out here to talk to you. Oh Uncle Jerry I
had to leave I hated it so much I couldn't
eat or sleep or anything. This is the
third school you've left my reason for. You
were are seems to me that you ought to
be able to make
a good one. I just don't seem to see it
in very well the kids all seem so oh I
don't know all they're interested in are
parties and clothes they seem to think
that's all there is to life. Alone
creatures I wish you'd talk to did you
listen to you. Or Sally you know your
father's Well then I ought to be home where I
can take care you ought to be in school
completing your education you want to make
something of your life to enjoy all of the
relation and and now I want to get down
to something serious. And good Jerry
you did promise you hanging on.
To that I'd help you when you were reading.
Your father want you to complete your
schooling for having me. Gerri dad's book
God wanted like the young ones too like
this but you might. You haven't
forgotten what it's like. Tonight.
The day I see my name. You know
the feeling don't you share.
Your sorrow to admit I do well with
them much more important than school or
anything else in the world.
Isn't it encouraging.
Third time. Yes I know.
Maybe we should pay to go
back. After all the shit it's all right
Jerry you can't keep on running away from
things or. A life. Where you can't
live another person's life for them
I had
a chance in fact. Alice grown up now I think
she ought to be allowed to do but she
wants to do I want her to
finish your education. Get
a chance to finish mine I always said
that any kid of mine was going to get the
right start in life. Well what's right
for one person isn't always right for
another Jim you. JERRY The trouble with
that girl is she's just plain states struck
. She comes by that
honestly another chick.
Member how we used to pound the sidewalks
and knock on doors nobody could.
Initially know that they were to try to.
Remember the House will be willing we
finally realized we were and. What right
if you were I do interfere with SALLY
SARA. Well what are we going to detain.
I give her
a pardon Sonny. Stochastic
father Gwen has been Castor. Oil
and. One night. When
is going to have some.
Coffee he instead of of fine is
a doctor of the will you have says just
another living skirt the law doctor.
When you. Get to be my age
you. Are clicking the kill.
Without. Your help that works out.
Who. Stole. Away my.
Name need to remotely dream I
know and never the truth seems
as though either the bloom. Have
now he's very well known or
a new hello after Harry. The charming
number I was just telling Harry how much I
liked it was fine lyric you've
written of thanks. Jerry
I've just been talking to Mr Dylan
and he thinks that who should be
a big production numbers for the school
and that of course Mary sing. Very.
Well and of course we'll have to
do it in time puts me in rather
a tough position though I ask after all I
did write it for Sally I know you to jeer
a bit look at Sally something else. She's
going to be awfully disappointed. It's
a wonderful song I'd love to sing and. I
hate to take it away from well it's for
the good of the show. I think
you're right ask. Have you
start though how you're going to
tell Sally it's not going to be easy
a lie but you should tell it you are.
Fragile would after all you know or so well
it shouldn't be too
difficult Well it would be
a lot easier if I didn't know it
so well. Would you like me to
tell you I'm sure she'll understand would
you do that man or certainly ask her to
meet me in my dressing room and don't
worry Thank you darling. But Uncle Jerry
wrote that song for me I know and I
know how disappointed you must be.
But Sally disappointments are part of the
theater and you've got to be able to take
them for the very same thing happened to
me in my first show I had to give up my
song with
a star I think I felt pretty much as
you're feeling right now then I think it's
a pretty low miserable trick for
you to pull on someone else.
Sally listen to me
a minute this is your first show you're
just starting and they're going to be
a good many songs and
a good many shows for you you may be
difficult for you understand now but one day
you'll realize you've got to give and
take how do you like it or not I'll never
take
a song away from anyone else especially
if it's their first real job Sally please
don't put this on
a personal basis I don't want to take the
song away from you know why are you doing
it Mr Darling and thinks it's best for
the show and what's best for the show is
more important what I want or you want or
any personal feelings involved. Don't you
see that So yes I see it all right you're
trying to take my song away from me you
are going to get away with it I'll go Jerry
wrote that song for me and I'm going to
sing it I don't care when you are the star
you're not going to take it away from
that salad. Kind of like going on Jerry
don't let me talk you into it you know what
I think that I'd like Dom.
I'm sorry Jerry.
But it's a challenge. And I
still shown courage and. Do
a lot of. It will have
a son. Took my song lay for me
the song you wrote for me shall
I there's
a little sing holds the image. And
efficiency very important here just.
As important. You didn't care what
happened the show just sort of
a mission got you way. To it it doesn't
work that way surely. Nothing works that
way. I learned something today. Said
realize that you're not ready for the.
Many. Trial you have to offer as
a small town radio currency in
return for which you once again.
I've known you loved you wish to live
because. I couldn't love you anymore if you
were my own child. I mustn't. You're
not going to get anywhere in this life
by using people. To.
Realize that and I can add
a mistake and anyone. That I. Wish.
To land. A.
War. I'm.
Already.
The
YOUR. Mom and.
I am an.
American in the army
Durham a running back and
Glen are blameless it is
a car. Relentless blackmail and
a lot of lead Melissa Moore
a. Girl that
a lot of their lives. In the world
a leg is. A lie and the last
in. The cold chill of
the solid. In the vein is the Dolmetsch
girl. I'll be
a little older. Well I am all of us I'll
gladly. Get filed last. Fall we're
all.
A little.
The or don't mind the way. The
game makes me dream all gave
me the I know can never one
hundred. One mile embodiment
middle of the During my
will be dead and the. Good
I answered yes to annihilate
you lot and get diluted with
no one much to lose it is.
During
.
The door. Along. With the door.
They met. Them all The
elite in the area where
I am all the place. Made me.
Love and. Then the love in the
world of the one little. Girl and
the little girl.
Child.
Thank.
You yes is one of.
The talking. Charlotte it.
May be sure it stays in bed
miss one of your enemy.
Start again just as
a mistake as this will be. It
is hard I would stay very long
Mr Hester could usually rest.
Well good evening. We
missed you at the end of.
Our. Challenge Gunter.
Airstrikes to. Come down from ten
hours. To remain.
There and going out on my home for a
perfect Sunday would be proud of me
a little of it is still
cool Cherry I still.
Told my fortune I should the
subject should be in the. Sally's.
Screeched candle but I
think I heard it. On the.
Jury shit shit shit way too young to
be. A legit don't you worry about this
outbreak of that which I probably
should have. Just assume the shit.
Going to hit you. Why don't you
get back if it gets read here.
I left no stone unturned trying to find
selling. Personal and private detectives.
The answer was always the same
no when it seemed. It was
a futile hunt. I tried to
keep Jim's hopes alive but.
I think again you. And then. One night.
He said.
I think Mr Kerr You bet it was right
away he's been asking for you.
Jim. I was
just driving by top.
To get you. Feeling that
a. Good all you
need.
Is that things will be popping. Into.
Action this year. No not directly. A
couple of very close to an average.
Then I'm going to see the one things that.
You know that finish that and have kept
you from that. For good. Years.
What about your out. Furniture
major. Issues just.
Posing as your. Just
a good. Thing and change you are
a genius Jim. You were here when you took.
Your wording really is. A.
Picture. The next year
is splitting the third
stage now wait
a minute let's get something
strange and I did. Continue
on your faith in me over
the protesters. And.
If we're going to start ending a bookcase.
I just watched another thing in
a second.
You're a great mentor. Spend
a privilege. Getting in on it music.
Is the fun part let's
not talk that way Jim
a couple of weeks you'll be back at
that piano screaming for more and more.
Spooks like capturing. Hearing.
My children. In general
pretty alright so if.
I said in
a couple of weeks why was
the laughing about. Half
the time each car.
Just occurred hardly closed the door but.
I was. Completely lost
completely helpless.
Jim was gone and. I had failed
in a failing and. I lost
a world with Jim's passion everywhere. I
want to I want to go. Remembering lost
out. Facing
a world memory I could be thinking
turned to music I began to feel that I
might never write again.
IMO this has been going on for
weeks. Ever since Jim died.
Is
a score to write to them. But certainly doesn't
sound like Jerry seems to have completely
lost heart have you had any words we know
that he has everything he ever had in
children. Well don't worry
about it if you turn up. Jerry
I'm worried most of. You know last week I
believe he's beginning to think he can't
write music anymore. Heartbreaking
to watch. But I. Have
a book here I'd like him to take
a look at. I've been commissioned to adapt
and write lyrics and. I think Jerry's
manager the music. I don't think. That's
hard to believe there's never been
a time as long as I've known Jerry
when you couldn't excite him with
a good story. Never been
a time in his life. You can try.
Oh fine. I've just tinkering
a little bit with the melody was
kind of the Old Course idea for
a new. Afghanistan.
KERRY. Thank you very. Much you know
I'll tell you what brought me out
here Gerri I came across a novel
that I think is going to make
a great show now if you do the music I'd
like to do the book after I I'd love to I
really would but. I have so many
commitments right now that I don't think I
wouldn't be fair to you are anyone concerned
suppose I leave the book with you when
you glance through it when you have time
it's no use asking Well I'll leave it any
day next week won't you take
a day or so they might do but I have
to get back to town by the door by.
Hello this is. Just
a moment Mr Kelly Jerry if
you can make you come down.
Lululemon Hello other.
Investors over Thought I'd probably get
funding they told us we'd. Like it right
thank you very much. Pleased to give you
the company didn't interest all this week
when you try to take
a days where you missed out and you
do that now called the. World.
In the air or. To
ask. First.
Born with the. Law or.
From that job or
a. One line no I did do you well one
more flood warning or
the real one LOL yeah I
moved to New Orleans where. The
thank you there were
a million dollars on no
more and then when I was
coming. Down in
a chair will they be washed it off. Rare.
A lot in order.
To. Corner.
What you're losing by constantly
refusing to die and. You D.-D.
I don't want friends. And yet
you stand there and shake your.
Head. And while I wait so next
Saturday as usual. And that seems
to on the. Day is love Brianna
I won't say any Don't
answer me I will day and don't and I
will damn this matter I am with you. My
heart full of blood my feet do things
age good do. You know want to see your
lovely. I don't love me I
don't want you to know me I'm
like an old fashioned way next
bump on the door. I feel so I'm
a lawyer standing on the
door. When you die. During
Hurricane Betsy when. The or was this
bailing isn't purely mental for Heavener
Runestone I'm not as bad as the.
Whole day and why should I I
will say an hour but I don't say
a metal scene or I know
but. Musically it's always
a little romantic. So it's by
a whole deal in my lawn the man.
Of the day after. Man.
I am just
a little sigh adult. Children
themselves.
Well. I am
a. Member
of them and. Am. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah yeah. Yeah.
Yeah yeah. Managed
man.
Yeah
I'm an.
Come in and. Out of code yet
every hour on areas of lead to
see. You doing here well I have
a front porch sure. Did you see
what we did you know. The fact is
not a soul is not a fact I liked it I was
a some of the people who think my music is
high brow can say that. I'm so excited I
don't know what to do you look wonderful
I'm coaching a lawyer Hanson is
a house and even though she's fine
but of course she misses you mine.
Too I miss you both. If she went you haven't
told me and what you're doing here I
know you're at a was
a New York and I'm here because somebody
to America find you I've been looking for
you for a long time as I.
Mentioned Not that I'm
a rival watcher you are but I promised your
father I'd look after you. Sally I want
you to come back to New York with me. I
can't encourage you. I'd like to but I
can't. And I'm. Glad about my father.
And
a realistic so because you know I never
would and then your intimate. When I I
heard about him it was as though. Some It
forced me to look in their office first
time. When I'm very much I knew I poked.
I was spoiled selfish and. I knew that I I
could live any respect for myself and I
did what I said I was going to
do. Like and then growing up.
On making my own way now I am pretty
good at it too. Where Elvis Aurea.
I just don't like the idea of you being
here. Just stepping stone from landing into
the ground on going. I'm
making fifty dollars
a week now because what management thing
I'm going to do with the final words or
I'll get one if not. On another one.
And on the chain. I'm not using it.
I mean. Thank you doing.
What you want to encourage.
Rest. You know knowing I'll give anything
in the world if you let me help you. But
I must say that I've never been quite
so proud of anyone in my life have you
explain. Why.
A coward.
Gradually I felt for you
heartache missed in a way I was
a beast. The promise I had made Jim had
been fulfilled Sally was going to be all
right. I walked along the river that
night with the river wind in my
face the taste of it on my
lips. And I. Stood there
listening. Sudden excited thrilling.
Element. That makes its way right to
the heart of that. And the voice of
that river with
a laugh the tears the joy.
The hope. Of all Americans.
Well that's my story. It's too bad Mr has
to look in the bin there tonight Mr Cohen
. He was and you. Can always be
a part of the music I. Never
had in the misselling.
Well I don't know exactly she's on
a row now. Maybe I'm just getting
something and this is James and.
He like giving and. Maybe my music
is ending to show ending after that
show tonight to K I gotta get you back
to Waldo you've got some balls to take.
Down with the kind you mean again and you
know. My opinion it's just the beginning
.
Of the. World or
a living faith she deems a no if
you didn't go stole the name of
a girl you are the world I want to be
a girl she was needed for the cade the good
luck to cheat the world I made up your
your get it it's not just the.
World Manya.
Your.
Heart. My ROM. Far
far off the murder.
Trial of.
Saddam or hard.
Hard.
Life. Was for him and. I heard the
loved her or her daughter was
in every street with. The last
man I saw the. Country
was dressed was. And
Lovers Walk been made was
to have been burgled solas.
I've gotten the same old taxi fare upset
a lot of blood but. Because
all the squeaky wheel was.
Moved one thing was when. I
saw. The hard truth or.
No matter how was I sure. Wish For.
And.
Will move further with.
Her.
All right.
Do sit down with the Carey Show we
won't be in the way of starting
a not not at all. Well I can't
get over this Mr on T.V.
We certainly don't grow stages like this
on Broadway. And I look at the size of
adult consent where you have everything
in the world to work with that's right Mr
We've tried to give you the best of
everything and that's so. What was the number
you're going to just say but we found
an old song which did first in one nine
hundred seventy called the line good songs
go awful had almost forgotten about that
or using it as
a frame for some of your other songs what
star is going to sing this well on the
screen as a matter of fact we're trying
out a new cover and you can this girl did
a test for us in New York and impressed
us so we threw out their chairs and done
much yet but we have great hopes for
a club like yours ready and ready for today
all right let's try to play and play it
like
a jolly that's why already
OK Well I'm back to. The
new evolution rationale really.
Early. We're
a.
Son of law firm. Pro
Shahrir. Son United.
We are. With Rose was very.
Good was. His brush or groom
always. Do we.
Run like a Mr. Like. I'm
a or I'd rather you say one of my
sons than anyone else and well Roger
Maris far off.
We're in a bomb Iran
a few good another R.L.
Early or hard the world.
War or. Red Sterling read.
The. A lot in
Iraq a sweet. Girl in
a
a. Bar or. Older
A A. Day are.
Or. Earl
off. Her or the
phone or go with Borini would
agree one. Hundred Nom the jury room here
is the way today is. The.
Only way you'll. Know we're
a world war Walworth Road.
During
a. A.
Roommate in your off.
Romance my friend her then
went to the UN and Raul
a little older. I lied I
will play bridge with my old
man a. New I haven't got
a chance. This is all funny or while my.
World.
Old. Movie
old to go bold moves through which green
toluene would move next lowly were.
Told. All the.
Lows liberals was. During.
World war on the brink of
a low voiced already
earn or my
heart. Surgeon named sawing
loan or lolol or
or. Loyalty girl out
a memo I hardly
a harmless little mole or warbirds
far away Duff.
Knoll. Olmos. Blow
all. Old blokes Amer
or mirror or war was so
no longer God.
Right where more or
nowhere.
Was. Gone cold war.
Was my out my vision. War More War
Why to live more. Now my
D.N.A.
More. I want her. Now not
hold or are watched pan
a small bomb I lose on
moon.
The poor who.
Heads Iraq war last met. The
blue maverick moon men. Who flew the
blood of water out of her.
Body. It was the absolute.
They must know stuff. But
they don't say nothing. He
just. Keeps on.
Tonight.
You know. I need to.
Run some it soon. But
oh I'm
a. Bit. Of
me questioning. Body go
away get married Greg
marry. That. Job you
know. Son.
In it. It leaves
a way.
That way we may find. A new food
fix with
a. I'm sorry the third man but I'm fairly
early February thirteenth.
Birthday her
emerged
the rare
Embury the low
there with their
marriage
I met
during. The during
their marriage.